<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>writing on hloh42 Journey</title><link>https://hloh42.github.io/tags/writing/</link><description>Recent content in writing on hloh42 Journey</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:18:55 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hloh42.github.io/tags/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>1st Dec 2025 2nd Entry Recursive Learning</title><link>https://hloh42.github.io/daily/1st-dec-2025-2nd-entry-recursive-learning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:18:55 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://hloh42.github.io/daily/1st-dec-2025-2nd-entry-recursive-learning/</guid><description>Being aware of learning as a recursive activity rather than a straight-forward one. Learning is not a one and done like most people assume it to be.And often it is less straight-forward than initially assumed.
Let&amp;rsquo;s take the learning goal of wanting to master git for the purposes of wanting to get better at cooperating as a software engineer.
But besides the layer of communication that happens at each level of push-pull , committing and branching.</description></item><item><title>1st Dec 2025 Entry - Writing Out Loud</title><link>https://hloh42.github.io/daily/1st-dec-2025-entry-writing-out-loud/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 18:56:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://hloh42.github.io/daily/1st-dec-2025-entry-writing-out-loud/</guid><description>This is my 10th post for chaining my writing behavior.
The one thing that I am reflecting on right now is that how clarity makes a difference in progress, when I have a clear picture of what to do and it removes the miasma of uncertainty , it allows me to leverage much more of my energy to execute on what matters and when I progress , it just feels so good especially if I feel stuck on it for quite some time.</description></item><item><title>29th Nov 2025 Entry</title><link>https://hloh42.github.io/daily/29th-nov-2025-entry/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:15:23 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://hloh42.github.io/daily/29th-nov-2025-entry/</guid><description>A natural stake.
The last few days I have been spending more time understanding html , css and Hugo rather than working on my writing.
It feels hard to concentrate and carry on your daily tasks if you know something is broken and it needs to be fixed and you are not quite up to knowledge or task yet to fix the issue.
Spending at least 3hr collectively + another 75 mins to finally understand what baseof.</description></item><item><title>26th_Nov_Entry</title><link>https://hloh42.github.io/posts/26th_nov_entry/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:11:51 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://hloh42.github.io/posts/26th_nov_entry/</guid><description>Learning to write a single point to the home well.
Today&amp;rsquo;s focus is on just leveraging on a single thing and doing that one thing well. Actually doing well for a certain skill requires you to operate wholeheartedly to support that single goal.
A simple goal may be to write every day like what I am trying to do right now, depending on the depth of skill required.
Just to write everyday consistently , I need to change a bunch of cues and habits to think and eat effectively to focus in the time needed to successfully fulfill this goal.</description></item><item><title>25th_Nov_Entry</title><link>https://hloh42.github.io/daily/25th_nov_entry/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:52:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://hloh42.github.io/daily/25th_nov_entry/</guid><description>List to do for fdf - estimated time 4 - 5 days + 3 evals ( 1 day ) Made massive progress for fdf today. Left the string parsing for hexdecimals, a centralized cleanup function similar to what was implemented in my pipex to clean up for the fdf data struct for all the points drawn on screen.
Having clarity around objectives and have a method and strategy to undertake the task is immensely helpful for the mind to focus on.</description></item><item><title>23rd Nov 2025 Writing Habit</title><link>https://hloh42.github.io/daily/23rd-nov-2025-writing-habit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 00:40:42 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://hloh42.github.io/daily/23rd-nov-2025-writing-habit/</guid><description>Introduction It has not been easily to be vulnerable , to take in all the mistakes I am making and will continue to make in pursuit of my goals. To be accepting of who I am and yet be seeking to be more. What a oxymoron it feels to be human and yet it feels like to be human is to be like this all the time.
To monitor one&amp;rsquo;s growth and thoughts over the time and effort it takes to transform, it is a really humbling path to be taking day-in and day-out.</description></item></channel></rss>